database = [
    {
        question: 'Select the most correct word: The fumes from the polluted truck were toxic to the (air, are)',
        optionA: 'Air',
        optionB: 'Are',
        answer: 'A'
    },
    {
        question: 'Select the most correct word: Have you (e’er, ere) had a New York pizza?',
        optionA: "E're",
        optionB: 'Ere',
        answer: 'A'
    },
    {
        question: 'Select the most correct word: She was an (err, heir) to an Egyptian pharaoh',
        optionA: 'Err',
        optionB: 'Heir',
        answer: 'B'
    },
    {
        question: 'Select the most correct word: The priest has placed the bible on the (altar, alter)',
        optionA: 'Altar',
        optionB: 'Alter',
        answer: 'A'
    },
    {
        question: 'Select the most correct word: The (be, bee) hive was dangerously close to the children.',
        optionA: 'Be',
        optionB: 'Bee',
        answer: 'B'
    },
    {
        question: 'The definition of ‘Engender’ is:',
        optionA: 'To bring into existence',
        optionB: 'Feeling or showing haughty disdain',
        answer: 'A'
    },
    {
        question: 'The definition of ‘Vitiate’ is:',
        optionA: 'Disinclined to exert oneself; habitually',
        optionB: 'To reduce the value or impair the quality of future impure',
        answer: 'B'
    },
    {
        question: 'The definition of ‘Pacify’ is:',
        optionA: 'To ease the anger or agitation of calm someone down.',
        optionB: 'Disfiguring damage',
        answer: 'A'
    },
    {
        question: 'The definition of ‘Dearth’ is:',
        optionA: 'A scarce supply; a lack',
        optionB: 'Disinclined to exert oneself; habitually',
        answer: 'A'
    },
    {
        question: 'The definition of ‘Indolence’ is:',
        optionA: 'To spend wastefully or extravagantly; dissipate waste',
        optionB: 'Being disinclined to exert oneself habitually',
        answer: 'B'
    }
]